Any characters, actions, places, organizations, professions and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
جميع الشخصيات أو الأفعال أو الأماكن أو المنظمات أو المهن أو الأحداث في هذه السلسلة خيالية ومصممة لأغراض الترفيه فقط.
They are not intended to guide or encourage any behavior in the story. Viewer discretion is advised.
لا تهدف هذه التعليقات إلى توجيه أو تشجيع أي سلوك في القصة. يُرجى مراعاة تقدير المشاهد.
Hey!
يا!
Get up!
استيقظ!
Punching like that's just gonna hurt your hand for nothing.
إن اللكم بهذه الطريقة سوف يؤذي يدك من دون أي سبب.
No one's as good as you!
لا أحد أفضل منك!
You keep talking nonsense.
تستمر في التحدث بالهراء.
Come on.
تعال.
One-two?
واحد-اثنين؟
Yeah. One-two. Come on!
نعم. واحد-اثنين. هيا!
Do it properly.
افعل ذلك بشكل صحيح.
You punch really weak.
لكمتك ضعيفة جدًا.
I've brought your order.
لقد أحضرت طلبك.
Who the heck!
من هو هذا الجحيم!
Hold on, bro.
انتظر يا أخي.
I'll grab it for you.
سأحضره لك.
Don't trouble yourself.
لا تتعب نفسك .
Drop it!
أسقطها!
Please pay up for me, bro!
من فضلك ادفع لي يا أخي!
What the heck?
ماذا بحق الجحيم؟
Please make the payment.
يرجى إجراء الدفع.
120 baht.
120 بات.
I didn't even eat, why do I have to pay?
لم أتناول الطعام حتى، لماذا يجب علي أن أدفع؟
Come on.
تعال.
Hey.
يا.
Go!
يذهب!
Go! Go!
إذهب! إذهب!
Hey, don't dodge!
مهلا، لا تتهرب!
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'm not giving you the money if you dodge!
لن أعطيك المال إذا تهربت!
Hell yeah!
نعم نعم!
Round's over, bro!
إنتهت الجولة يا أخي!
I was really getting into gear!
لقد كنت في الواقع في حالة تأهب!
Yo, little bro, how's it feel?
يا أخي الصغير، كيف تشعر؟
Well.
حسنًا.
I was just getting warmed up.
لقد كنت فقط أحصل على الإحماء.
Hey, it's gonna sting a little, bro.
مهلا، إنه سوف يلسع قليلا، يا أخي.
I'm okay, bro.
انا بخير يا اخي.
Where did I put my money?
أين وضعت أموالي؟
Here, bro.
هنا يا أخي.
Is there anything missing?
هل هناك شيء مفقود؟
It's complete.
لقد اكتملت.
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
My wife's gonna hit me harder than this.
زوجتي ستضربني بقوة أكبر من هذا.
If it weren't for you, I'd have no way to let off this steam.
إذا لم يكن الأمر كذلك بالنسبة لك، فلن يكون لدي طريقة للتخلص من هذا البخار.
Hey, Benz.
مرحباً، بنز.
Thank you. Thank you.
شكرا لك. شكرا لك.
- Let's go. - Yeah.
- دعنا نذهب. - نعم.
- Thank you. - You can use my service again.
- شكرا لك. - يمكنك استخدام خدمتي مرة أخرى.
Yeah.
نعم.
It's hurt.
إنه مؤلم.
Hey.
يا.
Don't freak out.
لا تقلق.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
انا لن أؤذيك.
I'm just here to talk to you.
أنا هنا فقط للتحدث معك.
How much do you still owe?
كم المبلغ الذي لا يزال عليك دفعه؟
300,000?
300000؟
Yes, Wao.
نعم هم.
Can I have a little more time?
هل يمكنني الحصول على المزيد من الوقت؟
Isn't it still not due yet?
أليس الوقت لم يحن بعد؟
But my boss has a short temper.
لكن رئيسي لديه مزاج سريع الغضب.
So he offered you a good solution.
لذلك قدم لك الحل الجيد.
Hey.
يا.
A simple task
مهمة بسيطة
you're familiar with.
أنت على دراية به.
If you agree to do this job,
إذا وافقت على القيام بهذه المهمة،
my boss will reduce your debt by a hundred thousand.
مديري سوف يقلل ديونك بمئة ألف.
No,
لا،
I'm not getting involved in this stuff anymore.
لن أتدخل في هذا الأمر بعد الآن.
Oh, you bastard.
أوه، أيها الوغد.
Suddenly you wanna be a good person, huh?
فجأة تريد أن تكون شخصًا جيدًا، أليس كذلك؟
An easy job with a hundred thousand grand,
وظيفة سهلة بمبلغ مائة ألف ألف دولار،
do you want the easy money,
هل تريد المال السهل؟
or will you have to take a million punches to pay off your debt?
أم ستضطر إلى تحمل مليون ضربة لسداد ديونك؟
I guess
اعتقد
you'll have to take punches until your next life.
سيتعين عليك تحمل اللكمات حتى حياتك القادمة.
It's definitely like that.
إنه بالتأكيد مثل ذلك.
Oh, boss. Hello.
يا رئيس، مرحباً.
Hey, jerk, grab him!
يا أيها الأحمق، أمسكه!
Where ya going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Grab him.
امسكه.
You make me tired.
أنت تجعلني متعبًا.
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
Damn.
اللعنة.
Hey, stop.
مهلا، توقف.
This bastard is ridiculously tough!
هذا الوغد صعب بشكل مثير للسخرية!
Let me check his bag.
دعني أتحقق من حقيبته.
Wow, you're so hardworking.
واو، أنت مجتهد جدًا.
Wow.
رائع.
Hey.
يا.
I'll just take this money as my earnings.
سوف آخذ هذه الأموال كمكسب لي.
H... Hey!
ه... هي!
Wao! No!
هم! لا!
Hands off!
ابتعد عن يديك!
I beg you!
أرجوك!
I said let it go, damn it.
قلت دعها تذهب، اللعنة.
You fucking bastard, you're really pissing me off, you ahole!
أيها الوغد اللعين، أنت حقا تغضبني، أيها الأحمق!
I need to pee right now.
أحتاج للتبول الآن.
Hey, grab him!
مهلا، أمسكه!
Grab his hand.
امسك بيده.
I'm gonna smash his hand to pieces. Damn.
سأحطم يده إربًا إربًا. اللعنة.
Which hand did you use just now?
ما هي اليد التي استخدمتها للتو؟
This side?
هذا الجانب؟
You're really brave with me, huh, Yim?
أنت شجاع حقًا معي، أليس كذلك، ييم؟
Here's your food.
وهنا طعامك.
What the fuck do you mean by food? I didn't order shit!
ماذا تقصد بالطعام؟ لم أطلب شيئًا!
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
You!
أنت!
Hey!
يا!
Hey, let's go.
مهلا، دعنا نذهب.
I'll make you pay, you bastard.
سأجعلك تدفع الثمن أيها الوغد.
Hey, are you okay?
مهلا، هل أنت بخير؟
Hey.
يا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Yim!
ثمانية!
What's going on? Why do you smell like pee?
ماذا يحدث؟ لماذا رائحتك تشبه رائحة البول؟
What happened to your face? You look like you wrestled a dog.
ماذا حدث لوجهك؟ يبدو وكأنك تصارع كلبًا.
You even lost a fight with a dog.
حتى أنك خسرت معركة مع كلب.
How did you know I fought with a dog?
كيف عرفت أني تشاجرت مع كلب؟
Have you ever fought a dog?
هل سبق لك أن قاتلت كلبًا؟
Even hurt this bad, you can still get on my nerves?
حتى لو كنت تؤلمني بهذا الشكل، هل لا يزال بإمكانك إزعاجي؟
Should I give you a slap?
هل يجب أن أصفعك؟
Hey! Hey!
مهلا! مهلا!
What are you guys fighting about!?
ما الذي تتقاتلون من أجله يا رفاق؟
If you want to fight, take it to the ring.
إذا كنت تريد القتال، فخذه إلى الحلبة.
Our boss didn't bring you up to be a gangster.
رئيسنا لم يربيكم لتصبحوا رجال عصابات.
You're older, why are you picking fights with this kid?
أنت أكبر سنًا، لماذا تبدأ في القتال مع هذا الطفل؟
Alright, go on. Let's split up and back to practicing!
حسناً، هيا بنا. لنفترق ونعود إلى التدريب!
Yim, follow me!
يم، اتبعني!
Take this before you kick the bucket.
خذ هذا قبل أن تركل الدلو.
If you have any problems, just tell me.
إذا كان لديك أي مشاكل، فقط أخبرني.
How's it going? How's your training coming along?
كيف حالك؟ كيف يسير تدريبك؟
Are you ready for tryouts?
هل أنت مستعد للتجارب؟
Train what?
تدريب ماذا؟
When you're not around, there's no one to train me.
عندما لا تكون موجودًا، لن يكون هناك من يدربني.
Because you are like this.
لأنك هكذا.
You are not serious.
أنت لست جادًا.
Let me see. Raise your guard.
دعني أرى. ارفع حذرك.
My guard?
حارسي؟
Yeah.
نعم.
So chill.
لذا استرخي.
Because you are like this.
لأنك هكذا.
I was just kidding, why are you so serious?
لقد كنت أمزح فقط، لماذا أنت جاد جدًا؟
Whose is this?
من هذا؟
These things?
هذه الأشياء؟
These are our rising star boxers' things.
هذه هي الأشياء التي يمتلكها ملاكمو النجوم الصاعدون.
At that time, our gym wasn't behind anyone.
في ذلك الوقت، لم تكن صالتنا الرياضية متأخرة عن أي شخص.
Was our boxing gym had fighters that strong?
هل كان لدينا في صالة الملاكمة مقاتلين أقوياء إلى هذه الدرجة؟
Where are they now?
أين هم الآن؟
They've retired.
لقد تقاعدوا.
What a shame.
يا للعار.
Back when our boxing gym was thriving,
عندما كانت صالة الملاكمة الخاصة بنا مزدهرة،
I was a rising star.
لقد كنت نجمًا صاعدًا.
I used my elbows and knees like this!
لقد استخدمت مرفقي وركبتي هكذا!
No one can beat me, seriously.
لا أحد يستطيع التغلب علي، بجدية.
Do you get it, Yim?
هل فهمت ذلك، ييم؟
Huh?
هاه؟
You just leave me talking to myself?
هل تتركني أتحدث مع نفسي فقط؟
[F.A.GROUP MUAYTHAI GYM]
[صالة ألعاب رياضية للمواي تاي من مجموعة فاجروب]
Punch!
لكمة!
Punch him!
إضربه!
Fight him back!
حاربه مرة أخرى!
What the fuck do you mean by food? I didn't order shit!
ماذا تقصد بالطعام؟ لم أطلب شيئًا!
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Hey.
يا.
Yim!
ثمانية!
Yim, why are you spacing out?
يم، لماذا أنت متباعد؟
Go! You're up next. Get in the ring!
انطلق! أنت التالي. انضم إلى الحلبة!
Keep your guard up!
حافظ على حذرك!
Get in guard!
كن حذرا!
Don't run!
لا تركض!
Yim! Fight him back!
يم! قاومه!
Yim! Fight him!
يم! قاتله!
Fight him back!
حاربه مرة أخرى!
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Isn't that enough to see the result?
أليس هذا كافيا لرؤية النتيجة؟
Hey, don't rush it. This might be Yim's final round.
مهلا، لا تستعجل. قد تكون هذه الجولة الأخيرة لييم.
Knock him out. Knock him out.
أضربه. أضربه.
Yim.
ثمانية.
Make sure you store everything and lock the door properly.
تأكد من تخزين كل شيء وإغلاق الباب بشكل صحيح.
The cut on your face has healed. Don't mess with others again.
لقد شُفي جرح وجهك. لا تُخالط الآخرين مرة أخرى.
Don't forget to grab my stuff when it comes.
لا تنسى أن تأخذ أغراضي عندما تصل.
Go!
يذهب!
Why is it so stiff?
لماذا هو جامد جداً؟
It's hurt.
إنه مؤلم.
Get into a solid stance first,
اتخذ موقفًا ثابتًا أولاً،
then punch the bag.
ثم قم بضرب الكيس.
Hey, I remember you.
مهلا، أنا أتذكرك.
That night.
تلك الليلة.
Yeah, don't thank me.
نعم، لا تشكرني.
Who the hell would thank you?
من الجحيم سوف يشكرك؟
You dumped me here,
لقد تركتني هنا
and the damn mosquitoes tore me up because of you!
والبعوض اللعين مزقني بسببك!
Damn.
اللعنة.
If I knew you'd nag like this,
لو كنت أعلم أنك ستزعجني هكذا،
I should've just ditched you there.
كان ينبغي لي أن أتركك هناك.
I was just kidding.
لقد كنت أمزح فقط.
Just kidding?
أنا فقط أمزح؟
I'm Yim.
انا ييم.
Thanks for helping me and dropping me off here.
شكرا لمساعدتي وإيصالي إلى هنا.
Honestly, you didn't have to help me.
بصراحة، لم يكن عليك مساعدتي.
It was just 4-5 losers.
لقد كانت مجرد 4-5 خاسرين.
I can handle it easily.
أستطيع التعامل مع الأمر بسهولة.
Look at you. You don't believe me?
انظر إليك. ألا تصدقني؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Fine!
بخير!
Wanna duel me then?
هل تريد أن تتبارز معي إذن؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Wanna duel me for a round?
هل تريد أن تتبارز معي في جولة؟
Come on!
تعال!
Oh yeah?
أوه نعم؟
You're dead meat!
أنت لحم ميت!
It's hurt.
إنه مؤلم.
You're crazy good! (dialect)
أنت مجنون جيد! (اللهجة)
Pardon?
عفو؟
Why are you that good?
لماذا أنت جيد إلى هذه الدرجة؟
You're better than a few fighters at my gym.
أنت أفضل من بعض المقاتلين في صالة الألعاب الرياضية الخاصة بي.
You mean...
هل تقصد...
you?
أنت؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Thank you so much for helping me that day.
شكرا جزيلا لك على مساعدتي في ذلك اليوم.
If you hadn't been there, I'd be beat to hell.
لو لم تكن هناك، كنت سأتعرض للضرب في الجحيم.
Yeah.
نعم.
Hey, wait!
مهلا، انتظر!
Don't leave.
لا تغادر.
Please teach me how to fight like that day again.
من فضلك علمني كيف أقاتل مثل ذلك اليوم مرة أخرى.
Please?
لو سمحت؟
No.
لا.
Huh? Why?
هاه؟ لماذا؟
Please train me.
من فضلك دربني.
Please.
لو سمحت.
No.
لا.
Please train me. Please?
من فضلك دربني. من فضلك؟
Please?
لو سمحت؟
So what do I get for training you?
إذن ما الذي أحصل عليه مقابل تدريبك؟
I'll give you this drink for free if you train me.
سأعطيك هذا المشروب مجانًا إذا قمت بتدريبي.
Okay?
تمام؟
Stop!
قف!
I'm gonna drop your rating.
سأخفض تقييمك.
If you don't train me, I'm gonna report you.
إذا لم تدربني، سأبلغ عنك.
I'm reporting you for ignoring the customer's needs.
أنا أبلغ عنك بسبب تجاهل احتياجات العملاء.
You...
أنت...
I'll bring a ghost to scare you!
سأحضر شبحًا ليخيفك!
I'm gonna tell my dog to bite you too!
سأطلب من كلبي أن يعضك أيضًا!
Do whatever you want,
افعل ما تريد
I can always beat you up later.
أنا أستطيع دائما أن أتغلب عليك لاحقا.
Hey, my drink!
مرحبا، مشروبي!
Aren't you supposed to bring it to me!?
ألا يفترض بك أن تحضره لي؟
How can you take it!?
كيف يمكنك أن تأخذ ذلك؟
Won't train me, and still trying to take my drink?
لن تدربني، وما زلت تحاول تناول مشروبي؟
But, what's his name again?
ولكن ما اسمه مرة أخرى؟
I was just about to ask…
كنت على وشك أن أسأل؟؟؟
Damn.
اللعنة.
Thank you,
شكرًا لك،
Kampanat.
ارتجاف.
My name is Yim.
اسمي ييم.
What is your name?
ما اسمك؟
Or do you want me to call you
أم تريدني أن أتصل بك؟
Kampanat?
ارتجاف؟
Your real name.
اسمك الحقيقي.
Stop acting like this.
توقف عن التصرف بهذه الطريقة.
I'm annoyed.
أنا منزعج.
Stop telling other riders to call me to deliver your food.
توقف عن إخبار الركاب الآخرين بالاتصال بي لتوصيل طعامك.
I just wanted to see you.
لقد أردت فقط رؤيتك.
Besides, I tipped my money to the riders.
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، أعطيت أموالي للراكبين.
Don't worry about them.
لا تقلق بشأنهم.
If you're so annoyed, just train me.
إذا كنت منزعجًا جدًا، فقط قم بتدريبي.
You're not suspicious of me at all, are you?
أنت لا تشك بي على الإطلاق، أليس كذلك؟
Why would I be suspicious of you?
لماذا أكون مشبوهاً بك؟
You don't seem like a bad person at all.
لا يبدو أنك شخص سيء على الإطلاق.
Alright,
على ما يرام،
if you really want me to train you,
إذا كنت تريدني حقًا أن أدربك،
then stop wasting your time on nonsense
إذن توقف عن إضاعة وقتك في الهراء
and start taking your training seriously.
وابدأ في أخذ تدريبك على محمل الجد.
After that, will you train me?
وبعد ذلك هل ستدربني؟
You have to start by jumping rope here.
يتوجب عليك أن تبدأ بالقفز بالحبل هنا.
1,000 times a day.
1000 مرة في اليوم.
I need to see you jump rope when I ride past here again.
أريد أن أراك تقفز بالحبل عندما أمر من هنا مرة أخرى.
If you don't do it,
إذا لم تفعل ذلك،
I won't train you.
لن أدربك.
1,000 times?
1000 مرة؟
Can't you just train me? (dialect)
هل يمكنك تدريبي فقط؟ (اللهجة)
Say what?
يقول ما؟
Can't you just train me?
هل يمكنك تدريبي فقط؟
1,000 times.
1000 مرة.
If you don't do it,
إذا لم تفعل ذلك،
I won't train you.
لن أدربك.
1,000 times...
1000 مرة...
Fine.
بخير.
Well, 1,000 times.
حسنًا، 1000 مرة.
I'm getting serious!
أنا أصبح جديا!
Just jump...
فقط اقفز...
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
Do it properly.
افعل ذلك بشكل صحيح.
Do you think you can finish jumping rope like that?
هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع إنهاء القفز بالحبل بهذه الطريقة؟
My name is...
اسمي هو...
Kamphan.
كامفان.
Kamphan?
كمفان؟
Who are you looking for?
من تبحث عنه؟
Me?
أنا؟
What did I tell you?
ماذا قلت لك؟
I told you I need to see you jump rope when I ride past here, didn't I?
لقد قلت لك أنني بحاجة إلى رؤيتك تقفز بالحبل عندما أمر من هنا، أليس كذلك؟
I just took out the trash.
لقد أخرجت القمامة للتو.
Are you here to learn boxing or to learn how to clean?
هل أنت هنا لتعلم الملاكمة أو لتعلم كيفية التنظيف؟
Hey.
يا.
I have to clean the boxing gym,
يجب علي أن أقوم بتنظيف صالة الملاكمة،
where am I supposed to get the money to pay off my debt?
أين من المفترض أن أحصل على المال لسداد ديوني؟
Enough.
كافٍ.
Stop changing the subject.
توقف عن تغيير الموضوع.
As we agreed.
كما اتفقنا.
I told you I need to see you jump rope when I ride past here.
لقد قلت لك أنني بحاجة لرؤيتك تقفز بالحبل عندما أمر من هنا.
What did I agree with you about?
بماذا اتفقت معك؟
1,000 times a day.
1000 مرة في اليوم.
Yesterday you jumped rope 850 times,
لقد قفزت الحبل 850 مرة أمس،
and today you slacked off with just 600?
واليوم كنت متراخيا مع 600 فقط؟
If you're not gonna take this seriously,
إذا لم تكن تنوي أن تأخذ هذا الأمر على محمل الجد،
I'm out.
انا خارج.
Hey.
يا.
How did he know?
كيف عرف؟
991, 92, 93, 94, 95, 96, 97, 98, 99...!
991، 92، 93، 94، 95، 96، 97، 98، 99...!
1,000!
1000!
That's it!
هذا كل شيء!
If you actually try, you can make it!
إذا حاولت فعلاً، فستتمكن من تحقيق ذلك!
I finished the jump ropes like you said.
لقد انتهيت من حبل القفز كما قلت.
Now can you train me?
هل يمكنك تدريبي الآن؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Tell me the reason why I should train you.
أخبرني السبب الذي يدفعني لتدريبك.
I've done what you told me to do. (dialect)
لقد فعلت ما قلت لي أن أفعله. (اللهجة)
Say what?
يقول ما؟
I've done what you told me to do.
لقد فعلت ما قلت لي أن أفعله.
I want to get better,
أريد أن أصبح أفضل
or else I'll die from being trampled one day.
or else I'll die from being trampled one day.
At least I can protect myself.
At least I can protect myself.
I want to be able to face the boxers in the ring, and Wao.
I want to be able to face the boxers in the ring, and Wao.
I wish I could fight them.
I wish I could fight them.
Hey.
Hey.
Look at my sincere eyes.
Look at my sincere eyes.
Please? Please train me.
Please? Please train me.
Yeah.
Yeah.
Are you gonna starting training today?
Are you gonna starting training today?
Go back and rest for now.
Go back and rest for now.
Let's start training tomorrow.
Let's start training tomorrow.
See you on the deserted road.
See you on the deserted road.
Hey, wait!
Hey, wait!
How do you know I'm slacking off when I jump rope?
How do you know I'm slacking off when I jump rope?
YES!
YES!
Woohoo!
Woohoo!
Where did you get these things!?
Where did you get these things!?
Did you come to question me or train?
Did you come to question me or train?
Train! Train.
Train! Train.
Go!
Go!
Where?
Where?
Get ready!
Get ready!
Come on.
Come on.
Okay. I'm ready!
Okay. I'm ready!
Are you gonna practice in that outfit?
Are you gonna practice in that outfit?
Sorry.
Sorry.
Hurry up. We will practice in this life.
Hurry up. We will practice in this life.
Please wait a moment.
Please wait a moment.
When you throw the punch,
When you throw the punch,
throw it straight like this.
throw it straight like this.
Okay. When you throw...
Okay. When you throw...
Okay.
Okay.
Bend your knees.
Bend your knees.
Yeah.
Yeah.
Snap punch.
Snap punch.
Twist your body more.
Twist your body more.
Look at your opponent's face.
Look at your opponent's face.
Punch.
Punch.
Hold on.
Hold on.
Can't you stop smoking?
Can't you stop smoking?
I stink.
I stink.
If you don't like it, just go back.
If you don't like it, just go back.
It's not good for your health.
It's not good for your health.
My health or yours?
My health or yours?
Your health!
Your health!
Do you still want to train?
Do you still want to train?
Yes.
Yes.
Go. Continue using your left hand.
Go. Continue using your left hand.
Yeah.
Yeah.
That's right. Maintain your balance and keep punching.
That's right. Maintain your balance and keep punching.
Okay.
Okay.
I'm exhausted.
I'm exhausted.
Try again.
Try again.
Lean forward a little more.
Lean forward a little more.
Go further!
Go further!
- Yes. More! - Hurt. I'm hurt!
- Yes. More! - Hurt. I'm hurt!
3... 2...
3... 2...
Who are you waiting for?
Who are you waiting for?
Me?
Me?
Look.
Look.
Do you see them over there?
Do you see them over there?
He has been waiting for you since the afternoon.
He has been waiting for you since the afternoon.
Who?
Who?
Damn!
Damn!
Why did Wao come here?
Why did Wao come here?
Damn.
Damn.
Now I can't practice.
Now I can't practice.
I put in so much effort to get ready today.
I put in so much effort to get ready today.
I guess we should head back separately.
I guess we should head back separately.
Bye.
Bye.
Hold on.
Hold on.
Come on, get on.
Come on, get on.
Huh?
Huh?
Where to?
Where to?
I told you to get on, so get on.
I told you to get on, so get on.
Here.
Here.
Do I have to wear it too?
Do I have to wear it too?
Yeah, safety first.
Yeah, safety first.
Your helmet smells weird.
Your helmet smells weird.
Let's go.
Let's go.
Where are you taking me?
Where are you taking me?
Don't you have to go to training?
Don't you have to go to training?
Are you sitting at the front?
Are you sitting at the front?
Sure thing.
Sure thing.
Let's go!
Let's go!
I let you ride with me all the time, why are you still so heavy?
I let you ride with me all the time, why are you still so heavy?
Stop whining.
Stop whining.
- Hurry up, I want to train now. - You blocked my key.
- Hurry up, I want to train now. - You blocked my key.
I'm in top form today.
I'm in top form today.
Go!
Go!
Don't block me. Lower your head!
Don't block me. Lower your head!
Yeah.
Yeah.
Wow.
Wow.
Where are we now?
Where are we now?
Are you ready?
Are you ready?
Huh? Ready?
Huh? Ready?
Why do I have to be ready?
Why do I have to be ready?
Aren't you gonna train anymore?
Aren't you gonna train anymore?
Take off your jacket.
Take off your jacket.
Yes, I will train.
Yes, I will train.
But can you tell me first?
But can you tell me first?
Where is this place?
Where is this place?
Alright.
Alright.
My house.
My house.
House?
House?
Wow.
Wow.
I'm tired. Can I take a break?
I'm tired. Can I take a break?
Yeah, you can rest now.
Yeah, you can rest now.
Here, your water.
Here, your water.
Nice.
Nice.
Thank you.
Thank you.
Uh.
Uh.
Why is it so quiet in your house?
Why is it so quiet in your house?
Who are you with?
Who are you with?
Me?
Me?
I live alone.
I live alone.
I don't like having a lot of people around. It's too chaotic.
I don't like having a lot of people around. It's too chaotic.
Alone?
Alone?
What about your parents?
What about your parents?
They're in another house over there.
They're in another house over there.
So I'm living here alone.
So I'm living here alone.
So it turns out you're Young Master Kamphan.
So it turns out you're Young Master Kamphan.
You're like a rag wrapped around crap!
You're like a rag wrapped around crap!
You're supposed to say it's wrapped around gold.
You're supposed to say it's wrapped around gold.
Just kidding.
Just kidding.
It's also yellowish. (dialect)
It's also yellowish. (dialect)
So they're interchangeable. (dialect)
So they're interchangeable. (dialect)
Huh?
Huh?
It's also yellowish.
It's also yellowish.
So they're interchangeable.
لذلك فهما قابلان للتبادل.
Oh.
أوه.
Come to think of it,
إذا فكرت في الأمر،
your house looks pretty rich.
منزلك يبدو غنيًا جدًا.
How come you became a delivery rider?
كيف أصبحت سائق توصيل؟
That's on me.
هذا عليّ.
Can't you just butt out?
ألا يمكنك أن تبتعد قليلاً؟
Wow.
رائع.
I'm just asking a little, no need to piss off at all. (dialect)
أنا فقط أسأل قليلاً، لا داعي للغضب على الإطلاق. (لهجة)
Huh?
هاه؟
I'm just asking a little, no need to piss off at all.
أنا فقط أسأل قليلاً، ولا داعي للغضب على الإطلاق.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Let's just say this is my personal preference.
دعنا نقول فقط أن هذا هو تفضيلي الشخصي.
I'll be back.
سأعود.
I'm gonna feed the dogs.
سأطعم الكلاب.
Oh, you have a dog?
أوه، هل لديك كلب؟
Wow...
رائع...
Young Master Kamphan.
السيد الشاب كامفان.
Such a warm-hearted guy.
هذا الرجل طيب القلب.
I'll be back.
سأعود.
Hey, wait.
مهلا، انتظر.
Can I play with your dog too?
هل يمكنني اللعب مع كلبك أيضًا؟
I don't care, I'll go anyway.
لا يهمني، سأذهب على أية حال.
Wait for me!
الانتظار لي!
Gimme your paw.
أعطني مخلبك.
Other paw! Good girl.
مخلب آخر! فتاة جيدة.
You're adorable!
أنت رائعه!
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
Hmm? What's your name?
هممم؟ ما اسمك؟
Khai Jiao.
خاي جياو.
Who asked you?
من سألك؟
I'm asking this little dog.
أنا أسأل هذا الكلب الصغير.
Right? Khai Jiao.
صحيح؟ خاي جياو.
Just kidding.
أنا فقط أمزح.
Khai Jiao. Khai Jiao. Khai Jiao.
خاي جياو. خاي جياو. خاي جياو.
Paw!
مخلب!
Just go back to practicing.
فقط العودة إلى التدريب.
What?
ماذا؟
Can't I play with the dog first?
ألا يمكنني اللعب مع الكلب أولاً؟
Why are you in such a hurry?
لماذا أنت في عجلة من أمرك؟
Can I play with her first?
هل يمكنني اللعب معها أولاً؟
Please?
لو سمحت؟
Well.
حسنًا.
Okay.
تمام.
Khai Jiao. Paw!
خاي جياو. مخلب!
Other paw!
مخلب آخر!
Other paw.
مخلب آخر.
Give her some snacks too.
أعطيها بعض الوجبات الخفيفة أيضاً.
Are there snacks too?
هل هناك وجبات خفيفة أيضاً؟
Here. Khai Jiao.
هنا. خاي جياو.
Not me!
ليس انا!
Oh, wrong one.
أوه ، واحد خاطئ.
Gimme your paw!
أعطني مخلبك!
Good.
جيد.
Nom-nom-nom.
الاسم-الاسم-الاسم.
Up!
أعلى!
Let's use the ‘up' command.
دعنا نستخدم الأمر ???up'.
Good girl. Khai Jiao.
فتاة جيدة. خاي جياو.
Why do I have this sharp pain?
لماذا أشعر بهذا الألم الحاد؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
- I don't know. - Let me check it.
- لا أعلم. - دعني أتحقق من ذلك.
Come on. I'll give you a massage.
تعال، سأعطيك تدليكًا.
Move over here.
انتقل إلى هنا.
I'll do the massage for you.
سأقوم بالتدليك لك.
Could it be a muscle spasm?
هل يمكن أن يكون تشنج عضلي؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
Suddenly, it gave a sharp pain.
فجأة، شعرت بألم حاد.
Yeah, right there!
نعم، هناك!
Great! Great! Great!
عظيم! عظيم! عظيم!
Great!
عظيم!
Great. Great.
عظيم. عظيم.
Exactly there.
بالضبط هناك.
You're so clever.
أنت ذكي جدًا.
Aren't you going to continue training?
هل ستستمر في التدريب؟
Hey, my arm hurts.
مهلا، ذراعي تؤلمني.
I have a sharp pain.
لدي ألم حاد.
Please continue massaging me.
من فضلك استمر في تدليكني.
Please. Please. Please.
من فضلك. من فضلك. من فضلك.
Fine.
بخير.